widgetpack.com 2017-04-29

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### General

While using this Site, you may need to feed-in personal information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, some unique characteristics that disclose your personality, such as: name, email, photo, likes and dislikes. 

WidgetPack web-servers automatically track and store Site usage data. This information is liable to include, but is not limited to, your computer’s IP. Along other sites, WidgetPack also uses “cookies” to collect such information. A cookie is an essential data file that is stored on your computer hard drive for record-keeping purposes allowing saving your registration ID and login password for prospective logins to WidgetPack Site; “session ID cookies” enable certain features of the Site providing authentication, identification of a user session, session contents and some other preferences. 

You can tweak your browser by changing its options to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use some of the Site’s features or all the functionalities of our services. 

We reserve the right, upon our own discretion, to change, modify, add, or tweak this policy at any time. WidgetPack will seek your best interests and concerns at any time when we have to change the guidelines, and seek to minimize changing the same materially. Site usage continuation subsequent to the any changes in this guideline indicate your acceptance of such changes, unilaterally. 

#### Handling Personal Information

Personal Information is only used as described in these Privacy Guidelines. 

WidgetPack utilize Personal Information for the following purposes: 

  * improve our Site features and workflow, services and content;
  * to better fulfill requests you may make of WidgetPack;
  * to personalize your Site interactions.

Personal Information is handled appropriately for technical purposes and is liable for de-identification for further use in order to monitor and analyze use of the Site and of our services and for the Site’s technical administration; to increase our Site’s functionality and user-friendly performance, to fine-tune performance to further meet user’s needs; to generate and derive useful system data, characteristics and website user-behavior, to verify that Site-visitors meet the technical criteria required to process their requests. 

#### Publicizing Personal Information

Personal Information voluntarily posted or cross-posted online on a publicly assessable blog or domain or divulged while commenting, may be viewed and used by others. We are not able to exert our control over such use of your Personal Information; and by using such services you single-handedly assume the risk. 

#### Safety and Security

WidgetPack cares about safeguarding your information. We go about reasonable measures designed to protect your information from an unauthorized access. Inasmuch as there are inherent risks in using the Internet - we cannot guarantee that your information is 100% secure outside your own precautions and discretion. 

WidgetPack, Inc.
